So let's see. The true positives are the points that
我们来看一下
真阳性是实际为阳性
are positive and the model correctly labels as positive.
且模型正确标记为阳性的点
These are the six blue points over here.
它们是这里的六个蓝色点
The true negatives are the points that are
真阴性是实际为阴性
negative and the model correctly labels as negative.
且模型阳性确标记为阴性的点
These are the five negative red points over here.
它们是这里的五个阴性的红色点
假阳性是实际为阴性
The false positives are the points that are negative
but the model incorrectly labels as positive.
但模型错误标记为阳性的点
它们是这里的两个红点
These are these two red points over here.
And finally, the false negatives are the points that
最后 假阴性是实际为阳性
are positive but the model incorrectly labels as negative.
但模型标记为阴性的点
就是这里这个蓝色点
That's just this blue point over here.
So there we go. That's the confusion matrix.
就这样
这就是混淆矩阵